let MCQS = [{
        question: "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
    choice1: "Humanity",
    choice2: "Health",
    choice3: "Honour",
    choice4: "Household",
    answer: "2",
    
    },  
    {
        question: "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
    choice1: "Pocahontas",
    choice2: "Sleeping Beauty",
    choice3: "Cinderella",
    choice4: "Elsa",
    answer: "3",
    
    },  
    {
        question: "Who was the youngest British Prime Minister?",
    choice1: "David Cameron",
    choice2: "William Pitt the Yonger",
    choice3: "Tony Blair",
    choice4: "William Cavendish",
    answer: "2"
    },  
    {
        question: "Who won the first ever football World Cup?",
    choice1: "Uruguay" ,
    choice2: "Brazil",
    choice3: "Portugal",
    choice4: "Sweden",
    answer: "1"
    },
    {  
        question: "What was the only painting sold by Vincent van Gogh during his lifetime?",
    choice1: "Sunflowers",
    choice2: "The Starry Night",
    choice3: "The Red Vineyard",
    choice4: "The Yellow House",
    answer: "3"
    },  
    {
        question: "How many million miles away is the sun from the Earth?",
    choice1: "93 million",
    choice2: "12 million",
    choice3: "136 million",
    choice4: "200 million",
    answer: "1"
    },  
    {
        question: "Which singer has a tattoo of Heinz tomato ketchup on his arm?",
    choice1: "Lewis Capaldi",
    choice2: "Martin Kemp",
    choice3: "Tom Jones",
    choice4: "Ed Sheeran",
    answer: "4"
     },
     {
        question: "Duroc, Berkshire and Mangalica are breeds of which farmyard animal?",
    choice1: "Chicken",
    choice2: "Cow",
    choice3: "Pig",
    choice4: "Sheep",
    answer: "3"
     }, 
     { 
        question: "Which city will host the 2028 Olympic Games?",
    choice1: "Beijing",
    choice2: "Paris",
    choice3: "Tokyo",
    choice4: "Los Angeles",
    answer: "4"
    },
    {  
        question: "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
    choice1: "Humanity",
    choice2: "Health",
    choice3: "Honour",
    choice4: "Household",
    answer: "2"
    },
    {  
        question: "What is the most sold flavour of Walkerâ€™s crisps?",
    choice1: "Cheese and Onion",
    choice2: "Salted and Vinegar",
    choice3: "Prawn Cocktail",
    choice4: "Ready Salted",
    answer: "1"
     },
     {  
        question: "What colour were the Pyramids of Giza originally?",
    choice1: "Orange",
    choice2: "Blue",
    choice3: "Pink",
    choice4: "White",
    answer: "4"
     },  

     ]